let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Palavra MESA ? ",
        answer: "Table",
        options: [
            "Desk",
            "Table",
            "Chair",
            "Bed",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Palavrea PÃO ?",
        answer: "Bread",
        options: [
            "Bread",
            "Butter",
            "Cheese",
            "Milk",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Palavra OLHO ?",
        answer: "Eye",
        options: [
            "Ear",
            "Nose",
            "Book",
            "Eye",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Palavra CHUVA ?",
        answer: "Rain",
        options: [
            "Water",
            "Enemy",
            "Rain",
            "Snow",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Palavra ÁGUA ?",
        answer: "Water",
        options: [
            "Water",
            "Run",
            "Fire",
            "Earth",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Palavra SOL ?",
        answer: "Sun",
        options: [
            "Moon",
            "Sun",
            "Star",
            "Cloud",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Palavra CORAÇÃO ?",
        answer: "Heart",
        options: [
            "Lungs",
            "Liver",
            "Brain",
            "Heart",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Palavra TRABALHO ?",
        answer: "Work",
        options: [
            "Play",
            "Work",
            "Study",
            "Rest",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Palavra JANELA?",
        answer: "Window",
        options: [
            "Door",
            "Window",
            "Wall",
            "Roof",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Palavra FLORESTA?",
        answer: "Forest",
        options: [
            "Mountain",
            "River",
            "Forest",
            "Desert",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Palavra VEGETARIANO ?",
        answer: "Vegetarian",
        options: [
            "Meat-eater",
            "Vegan",
            "Carnivore",
            "Vegetarian",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Palavra SAUDADE?",
        answer: "Longing",
        options: [
            "Nostalgia",
            "Happiness",
            "Longing",
            "Regret",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Palavra CONHECIMENTO?",
        answer: "Awareness",
        options: [
            "Thought",
            "Awareness",
            "Effervescent",
            "Consciousness",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: " Palavra ESQUiZOFRENIA ?",
        answer: "Schizophrenia",
        options: [
            "Psychosis",
            "Bipolar disorder",
            "Schizophrenia",
            "Paranoia",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Palavra ATADURA?",
        answer: "Band-Aid",
        options: [
            "Band-Aid",
            "Plaster",
            "Cast",
            "Gauze",
        ]
    },
]